恭喜您，您已经完成了本课程关于Linux文件的这一部分
So congratulations you've made it to the end of this section of the Course all about the Linux file
系统不能有效地导航Linux文件系统和处理文件很可能会导致
system not being able to effectively navigate the Linux file system and work with files is likely going
成为你会反复使用的技能。
to be skills that you will use over and over and over again.
所以祝贺你走到这一步。
So congratulations for making it this far.
所以。
So.
因此，为了庆祝您到目前为止在本视频课程中取得的成功，请快速回顾一下我们所拥有的内容
So to celebrate your success so far in the course in this video have a quick review of what we have
在这一节中介绍，这样您就可以看到您已经走了多远。
covered in this section so you can see just how far that you have come.
好的。
OK.
所以我们首先讨论一下美国系统的文件结构，对不起。
So we first started off with a discussion of the structure of the file structure of the US system sorry.
您可以看到，整个文件系统都有一个树状结构，从根目录开始
And you saw that the whole file system has a tree like structure starting with a root directory and
从那里向外延伸。
branching out from there.
一旦您了解了文件系统的结构，并且有了可以使用的映射，您就会了解
And once you understood that the structure of the file system and had a map to work with you learned
如何使用pwd命令告诉您的shell当前在哪里运行，PWT将发出声音
how to tell where your shell is currently operating from using the P WD command that PWT sounds will
打印工作目录，它基本上会在屏幕上打印出您的shell当前所在的位置
print working directory and it basically prints out on your screen the location that your shell is currently
在这里操作。
operating in.
您还会了解到，您可以通过浏览shell提示符来做同样的事情，该提示符的
And you also learn that you can do the same thing by glancing at your shell prompt which the bit of
在您输入命令的左侧终端中输入文本。
text in your terminal on the left where you enter your commands.
好的。
OK.
现在，一旦您了解了如何找出您所看到的位置，您就必须在文件系统中移动并更改
Now once you saw how to find out where you while you saw had to move around the file system and change
目录使用cd命令我必须通过使用cd命令列出目录的内容来查看
directories using the cd command I had to look around by listing the contents of directories using the
L%s命令。
L s command.
现在，在学习了这些关键导航命令之后，您对文件的含义进行了讨论
Now after learning these critical navigation commands you had a discussion about the meaning of file
Linux中的扩展名，您可以看到文件扩展名在X中并不重要，但对于
extensions in Linux and you saw that file extensions don't matter much in X but might matter to the
在上面运行的程序。
programs running on it.
这意味着您可以灵活地为文件指定您想要的任何名称，但请记住
This means that you have the flexibility to give files whatever names that you want but remember that
您可能希望坚持标准的文件约定。
you might want to stick to standard file conventions.
如果您希望其他程序使用这些文件，那么您了解了
If you're expecting those files to be used by other programs then you learned about a feature of the
我相信你现在已经爱上的外壳是通配符。
shell that I'm sure you fell in love with by now which is wildcards.
现在，通配符允许您一次操作许多不同的文件，并且只需专门操作
Now wildcards allow you to operate on many different files at once and just operate on specifically
您要寻找的是什么，它可以为您节省大量时间和打字时间，而且它基本上会使您的
what you are looking for which is which saves you lots of time and typing and it basically makes your
指挥的力量要强大得多。
commands a whole lot more powerful.
现在，一旦你记下了这些非常重要的基础知识，你就学会了一大堆命令。
Now once you had got those very important basics down you learned a whole bunch of commands.
我必须创建文件和目录，复制它们，粘贴它们，删除它们，重命名它们，移动它们。
I had to create files and directories copy them paste them delete them rename them move them around.
此外，我还必须使用基于命令行的文本文件编辑器Nano对它们进行编辑。
And also I had to edit them with a command line based text file editor called Nano.
但是，随着所有这些文件的创建、移动和编辑，很可能在某些时候您不会
But with all of this creation moving and editing of files it's quite likely that at some point you won't
确切地知道文件的创建位置或位置，您可能需要找到它。
know exactly where a file is created or located and you might need to find it.
因此，您可以使用LOCATE命令查找系统上的文件，并且可以让LOCATE命令使用
So you use the locate command to find files on your system and you'll have the locate command uses a
数据库来查找文件，并且您了解了如何使用update dbi命令来更新其数据库以确保安全性。
database to find files and you saw how to use the update DBI command to update its database for security
更新数据库需要普通用户没有的提升权限的原因。
reasons updating the database requies elevated privileges that normal users don't have.
那么，如何使用sudo命令临时成为root用户并执行您需要执行的操作呢？
So how do you use the sudo command to temporarily become the root user and do what you need to do.
您可以将其用于任何命令，而不仅仅是LOCATE命令。
And you can use that for any command not just the locate command.
现在，虽然定位命令非常棒，但您可以快速完成工作。
Now although the locate command is awesome you can get the job done quickly.
有时你需要一些更具定制化和重用性的东西。
Sometimes you need something a bit more customizable and heavy duty.
因此，在了解了LOCATE命令之后，您将了解如何使用find命令查找文件
So after learning about the locate command you learn how to find files using the find command that find
命令是一个功能非常强大的命令，它有很多选项可以确保您可以找到
command is a super powerful command that has loads of options to make sure that you can find what ever
你想在你的系统上。
you want on your system.
它还有一个额外的好处，那就是一旦你发现了一堆董事的文件
There it also has the added bonus that once you have found a bunch of files of directors with the find
命令您实际上可以告诉find命令在该命令或每个命令的一系列命令下运行
command you can actually tell the find command to run under the command or series of commands for each
它找到的结果。
result that it finds.
这使您可以很轻松地创建令人难以置信的强大功能。
And this allows you to create incredibly powerful functionality with very little effort.
然后，您将继续学习如何使用cat命令查看文件内部，这样您就可以
And then you moved on to learn about how to look inside files using the cat command so that you can
还可以使用cat命令将文件粘合在一起或连接不同的文件，有时您需要
also stick files together or concatenate different files using the cat command and sometimes you need
要反转数据，请执行以下操作。
to reverse data.
因此，您看到可以使用Attack命令垂直反转文件，也可以使用
So you saw that you can reverse files vertically using the attack command or horizontally using the
指挥部。
command.
现在，有时当您打开文件或运行命令时，您会在屏幕上看到大量输出，并且
Now sometimes when you open files or run commands you get a whole lot of output on the screen and having
一下子出现在屏幕上是没有多大帮助的。
all on the screen at once is not very helpful.
因此，您了解了最后一页，该程序允许您浏览大量文本以
So you learnt about the last page a program that allows you to page through large amounts of text to
让它更易于管理，你还学到了一大堆有用的策略，让你得到你想要的
make it more manageable and you also learned a whole host of useful tactics for getting just what you
想要从一个文件中。
want from a file.
head命令、ail命令和grep命令也是如此，然后您了解了如何对文件内容进行排序
So is the head command the tail command and grep command then you saw how you can sort of files content
以各种不同的方式。
in a variety of different ways.
最后，我们在讨论的最后介绍了文件归档和压缩。
And finally we topped off the discussion with a look at file archiving and compression.
你在这一节真的学到了很多东西，你应该为自己感到无比自豪
So you've really learned a lot of stuff in this section and you should be incredibly proud of yourself
太好了。
so well.
9~10成熟。
Well done.
现在你将使用你在这里一直学到的技能。
Now you will use the skills that you've learned here all the time.
我们都在做这方面的工作，现在它已经上线了。
We all work with that and it's come on line.
所以现在在您的Linux技能发展过程中，这真的是一个令人惊叹的时刻。
So it's a really amazing moment right now in your Linux skills development.
因此，在下一节中，您将了解如何在系统上计划和自动执行任务
So in the next section you're going to learn about how you can schedule and automate tasks on your system
使用bash脚本和一个名为Kramm的非常有用的实用程序。
using bash scripts and a super useful utility called Krumm.
但在我们谈到那之前我有个项目要你完成。
But before we get to that I have a project for you to complete.
现在，该项目将挑战您如何使用Linux文件系统做各种事情，并使用一大堆
Now the project will challenge you to do various things with the Linux file system and use a whole bunch
并建立一条真正先进的管道。
of the commands and build a really advanced pipeline.
好的，现在它将会很棒，它将作为一种荣誉的徽章，因为你已经学到了所有的东西
OK now it's going to be awesome and it will serve as a badge of honor that you have learned everything
我们已经在课程的这一节中介绍了这些内容，这样您就可以放心地继续学习了。
that we've covered in this section of the course so you can feel confident moving on.
在下一个视频中，我将给你们一个项目简介。
So in the next video I'm going to be giving you a project brief.
再次祝贺你们在这一节中所做的令人惊叹的工作。
So congratulations once again for what you've done in the section you're doing amazingly.
我为你感到非常骄傲，我会在下一个视频中见到你。
I'm super proud of you and I'll see you in the next video.